welcome back everyone
today you should get ready for more craziness
since we are going to use a bunch of eyes of harmony to contain multiple universes
crafting one of those takes a lot of time
and many machines which we used to tink were already expensive on their own
and it will also take some new blocks which are just as much expensive
and all of those blocks will recursively contain other expensive stuff
also
we need some parts that are rather slow to process
even with our extruder powered by 8 UMV energy hatches
thus we shall build more of those
which means we will be needing more energy hatches
and what we now lack off is water
so we have to look into a proper source of water
and a kitchen sink doesn't seem to work properly
luckily
the reservoir hatch seems to work well enough
if we give it enough time to stock up fluid in a second storage
now that we have water
we can start working on fixing the next issue
assembly lines
our old generic setup has a couple of issues
when crafting slow things
new things can queue up
and end up having to wait too much time
so we shall expand it
but
this time we will use advanced assembly lines
those will leave some items in the buses locking the usage
also those can do parallel crafting when the conditions allow for it
but doing parallel while also allowing for multipurpose crafting has its caveat
requiring a more complex setup we may see later on
anyways
we now got to the point of researching the main block of the eye of harmony
which is starting to require a lot of computation
and while we get the research done
we can also get the crafting items ready
once we got to the point of crafting it
we realized that this is going to take too much time
we have no hurry for that
but since this is using relatively no power
we can overclock it
don't worry about voiding the crafting
since this is an advanced assembly line
we only lost the first item and the fluids
meaning a bunch of space elevators and neutronium
to overclock it
we shall use a laser hatch
that can bring half of our total energy production
this assembly line is going to work with a single slice
so it won't use more than 3 percent of our production
meanwhile we also have a bunch of assembly lines
with dedicated recipe for parallelization
those are probably going to be working way more often and at full capacity
so we throttle them by lowering the amperage
and to get those amounts of power in that place
we will need a better capacitor
which we shall place in a dedicated nearby LSC
with that
we can now start crafting things that
will use one Dyson sphere of power for 45 seconds over 16 steps
meanwhile using 3 Dysons of power
we can quickly craft the other parts
however before getting to that point
we had to fix a couple of things
the last step of the crafting was supposed to be time consuming
but the other steps are resource intensive
and the main issue was our circuit production
those things are so clogged
that the issue even falls to our crafting network storage
thus it is time to increase the size of our circuit factory
and that was the first floor of circuit production
so we slowly work through each of the floors of our factory
which was overall quite easy thanks to the newly discovered tools
with those new circuits
we can quickly finish up the crafting of our first eye of harmony
and this is one more multi block with special requirements
the first being the need to change our game UI size
to properly see what it does
from a single run of that thing
we are going to get huge amount of every kind of resource
but what we care about is
the condensed raw stellar plasma mixture
and white dwarf matter
however
the recipe time is really high
and takes more inputs than we can input in a single tick
so we will probably look into some overclocking for the first few iterations
to help us with that and other future planning
we can use this helpful spreadsheet suggested by the quest book
all is left to do is to load up the eye of harmony with the input fluids
which will take some time
once it has enough
we can turn it on
however
it looks like it's not going to produce anything
and that is because we've fed it too much fluid
and the meaning of that fancy formula is that
you get nothing if you insert 5% fluid more than needed
so to insert exact amounts
we shall use a convoluted system that involves ae2 and crafting cards
after slowly charging up the machine
we managed to make it run with full output
and with a recipe that will finish in less than an hour
and that overclock took the power we accumulated in a couple of days
anyways
that machine is still in its crude state
we want to upgrade it at least to perfect
if we want to produce molten universium
the material used in any UXV part
however
getting a perfect eye of harmony requires black dwarf matter
which can be obtained from the advanced tier onwards
to get those
we lack of white dwarf matter and infinity
we have already built a lot of DTPFs
so we shall look for a better way
such as upgrading one with a transdimensional alignment matrix
that thing will speed up our Infinity production by 20 times meanwhile
the white dwarf matter has become a major issue
our production is already too low
and our power production can't even keep up with that little production
to get a better understanding of the situation
we can go back to our spreadsheet
and see how our energy production and objective progress varies in function of overclocks
and getting the tier 4 eye of harmony like that is not going to be okay
to increase the production there are many ways
an interesting one is upgrading the time dilation field generators
Thus cutting in four the time required
but with a 20% chance of recipe failing
the issue is that those will cost white dwarf matter
but a more reasonable amount
that will still take some time
which we can use to further upgrade our power production
with all of that time at our disposal
we managed to build more than 100 Dyson Spheres
enough to fill an ultimate battery in three hours
and once we manage to gather enough white dwarf matter
we can upgrade our time dilation field generators to tier 3
which will yield around 3 times more than the tier 1
and to round up our production to 1 milli-bucket per second
we can use the leftover parts on a second eye of harmony
and to avoid having to build a second convoluted gas loading system
we have split the complex part
in a way that can be shared across multiple machines
anyways as said
we are now producing white dwarf matter 4 times faster
but it's still not enough to reach the tier 4 in a reasonable amount of time
tier 4 is required for the black dwarf matter
but for a fifth of the cost we can move to tier 3
while on the current setup
it doesn't make a huge difference
it will allow for usage of tier 3 dimensions
which won't make black dwarf matter yet
but will make huge amount of white dwarf matter
allowing for faster tier 4 progression
so while we wait a couple of hours for the missing materials
we can go and take a trip inside one of our pocket universes we have created
where we can admire the creation and destruction of the stars
from which we extract the dwarf matter
and after exploring multiple microverses
we gather enough materials
to increase the tier of our spacetime compression field generators
which means that we can now contain tier 3 dimensions
thus making 4 times the amount of white dwarf matter
the issue now has become our assembly lines again
we are not using those at their full potential
we have some generic ones
which are not using the parallel feature
and other specific that require to manually set the filters for the recipe they do
however
we just noticed a feature that could help us fix all our issues
and make the perfect assembly line setup
a setup that will allow for multi recipe parallel crafting on multiple assembly lines at once
explaining how it works doesn't fit in this video
but you can just admire here how nicely it works
and that is just one of the many assembly lines that will manage slow craftings
we will want more of those
but while making it
we already finished the tier 4 eye of harmony
this will make black dwarf matter
but with those settings
the production is too low
so we made more eyes of harmony
to stock up a lot of white dwarf matter for other upgrades
the perfect tier of harmony requires quite some black dwarf matter
so let's see how we can get to it
as of now
that would take approximately 100 hours
and on a power loss
which we could fix by making a bunch more of Dyson Spheres
we could speed up the process by making more tier 4 eyes
but then we would probably have to lower the overclock setting
the best option is probably to do one step at a time
thus working on a tier 5 eye of harmony
which will allow for a faster tier 6
at that point
we notice that our success rate is getting too low
we can trade some yield to increase it
and once we have the tier 6
we will be able to work on the tier 7
but we will probably want to first make a bunch more of tier 6
and lower the overclocking
and of course
mass producing those machines like that
started to be heavy for our experimental assembly line
so we had to add a bunch more
which we are now connecting wirelessly
and with that
we now have a bunch of eyes
which finally managed to produce some universium
to use it
we shall start by solidifying it into ingots
which we then extrude into blocks
with those
we can now make universium nanites
which have many usages
but the main one is going to be making
magnetohydrodynamically constrained star matter
which is used in all of the parts and components of the next and last tier
but there are still a couple of materials we still don't have access to
the first one is eternity
to get that stuff
we start by acquiring some time pieces
then we add a group of Universium Nanites
to get the Temporal Harmonizer Catalyst
this will allow us to produce eternity
but it will use some chronic singularities
which we will be able to make easily using some eternity
but for the first iteration
we have to go with the more expensive way
also
to get more eternity out of our recipe loop
we can add some fermium and neptunium plasma
the other main ingredient for the next tier is magmatter
this stuff is produced in the heliofusion excisiter Gorge module
however
making it is not as easy as it might seems
to begin with
we have to unlock the last upgrade of the forge
and that is going to take a lot of Graviton Shards
which means we have to use our forge more to reach more milestones
an easy want to do is to process some more stuff
since we have different issues doing it as a single step
we shall split the task to multiple CPUs
and it turns out that
making a quarter of integer 32 steel ingots took a single tick
we repeat the process a bunch of times
to get our new shards
however those didn't get us far
so we retrieve some from unneeded upgrades
then after making one more upgrade
which also took all of our really ultimate batteries
we again run out of shards
luckily
there is a weird looping recipe
that can make us easily melt overflowing amount of stuff
however
we now maxed out the conversion milestone
and need to do something else
like heating up some nitrogen
heating it up to plasma uses quite a lot of power
thus helping us reach the next charge milestone
with that
we are now in front of the last upgrade
the main issue here is the crazy amount of batteries we need
currently
the only thing we lack of to craft those is some heavy radox
but let's get things more in perspective
crafting those batteries is a recursive process
meaning that the situation gets exponentially worse
luckily
we unlocked a better way of making batteries
that hugely cut the cost
however
that still used up the same amount of components that heavily use naquadria
since we couldn't produce enough
we have been integrating with some heavy radox
we could increase its production
but there is a better way of solving this issue
we can do an even higher skip
by using some of the newly acquired materials
but that is going to take quite some universium
so we better keep an eye on that
or maybe even more than one
actually let's be specific
to get the 10 million universium required in less than a day
we'd need 100 maxed out eyes of harmony
so for the moment
we better off find a better way of making Naquadria
increasing our ore or collection is the main way
but there's something else we can do
by adding some catalysts to our quantum force transformer
we can increase the output
and also focus more of the outputs to the one we care about
and that was the only thing we lacked of to craft the required batteries
then we spent some time AFK
to unlock the next catalyst milestone
so that we have enough shards to complete the path
that will allow us to process mag matter
however producing such materials is not as easy
as throwing random stuff in a machine
after getting an heliofusion exotizer in magmatter mode
we have to complete its mini game
once started
this machine will give us a tiny pile of some expensive materials
followed by some drops of space time products
to get magmatter
we have to send back the difference between the two fluids as ingots of the material of the tiny dust in plasma form
so we quickly improvise a way of quickly getting the needed plasma
and give it back to the exoticizer
with also the other two fluids it gave us
and with that
we have finally obtained our first magmatter
the issue now is finding a way of automating that process
and maybe
that actually is as easy as throwing random stuff at a new machine
all we have to do is make sure
it always has any of the 14 different plasmas at its disposal
and we can loop back the other two fluids
since we won't be doing any math with that setup
now that we have magmater
we can finally work on the UXV components
and I got to say
this is a really sophisticated motor
since not only it contains wetware mainframes in some of its winding
it also contains ultra high tier electrical circuitry inside the balls of its bearings
anyways
after quickly researching UXV energy hatches
we upgrade our implosion compressor
this will allow us to unlock all the recipes
such as the one that will cut in half the universium cost
when making magnetohydrodynamically constrained star matter
then to further reduce material usage
we will want a UXV component assembly line
but we are quickly reminded that our universium production is quite low
so we start crafting our first max out eye of harmony
all made out of gallifreyan parts
that thing is now so powerful
that it can contain one whole  solar system
and not only will it give off huge amounts of any raw material present in the game
it will also produce more energy than it uses
and to load it at a decent speed
we now have access to the humongous input hatch
but that thing still produces only 1.6 liters of universium per second
and to get just one UXV component assembly line
we need 27 millions of liters of that stuff
it doesn't take much to understand that we are going nowhere
even if we were to spam more of those machines
so we have to research for something even better than the best tier
and we came up with one quite interesting solution
the astral fabricator array
those things are meant to be inserted inside an eye of harmony to add parallelism
with some downsides
the first one we notice is that
the power output goes negative
but working in that mode will consume raw stellar plasma mixture
and we will be going negative on that stuff too
that is caused mostly by the low success rate
but we can downgrade one time dilatation field generator
to go back to positive production
now it is just a matter of figuring out
how many astral array we will need to get a good enough source of universium
and how to keep up with the power consumption
anyways
since our old setup isn't making enough materials
we tear it down so that we can recycle it
to make our first astral array
and that thing alone
with an almost maxed out eye of harmony
is already going to make 5 times as much as our old maxed out eye
but that is still not enough
thus we started the mass production of Astral Array fabricators
and with that
we are now exponentially increasing our universium production
or at least we were until our batteries run dry
but we managed to complete our UXV component assembly line just in time
as usual
this machine will make us use way less materials for each component
this time we even skip the compressing of the materials
but we still have to insert part of the circuits
anyways
now that we have completed all of the UXV stuff
and unlocked everything in the pack
there is only one last challenge left for us
but I think that's something we can do in the next episode
and the lesson today
is to always keep the coolest stuff hidden
so we can have an even greater last episode
bye bye
欢迎回来
今天可要准备好“疯狂”连击
因为我们要用一些鸿蒙之眼来收容多重宇宙
做一个EoH就需要大量时间
用于制造它的机器已经足够昂贵了
它还需要一些同样昂贵的新方块
所有这些方块都包含其他昂贵的东西
而且
我们需要一些加工速度相当慢的零件
即使是有八个UMV能源仓的压模机也不行
所以得上数量了
也就是说我们需要更多的能量仓
我们现在缺少的是水
所以我们必须寻找合适的水源
厨房水槽似乎不能正常工作
幸运地
蓄水仓工作良好
只要我们给它足够的时间在子网储备液体
现在我们有水了
我们可以开始解决下一个问题
装配线
我们旧的通用设置有几个问题
在制作缓慢的东西时
新材料会排队
最终会浪费大量时间在等待上
所以我们将扩展它
但是
这次我们将使用进阶装配线
它将会在仓室中进行锁定合成
条件允许的时候也可以并行合成
但是在对通用装配线进行并行处理时
有值得需要注意的地方
稍后便可以看到所需的复杂设置
不管怎样
我们现在要研究鸿蒙之眼的控制方块
这需要大量的算力
在我们完成研究的同时
我们也可以准备好材料
一旦开始准备制作
我们意识到这需要太多时间
我们不着急
但由于它相对来说不需要能量
我们可以超频
不用担心材料被吞
因为它是进阶装配线
我们只丢失了第一个流体和第一个物品
也就是一堆太空电梯和中子
要超频它
我们将使用激光仓
灌入基地一半的发电量
这条装配线将进行单片工作
所以它的消耗不会超过3%的总发电
同时我们还有一堆装配线
运行特定的配方来实现并行
这些可能会更频繁地满负荷工作
所以我们通过限制电流来省电
为了在那儿缓存如此大的能量
我们需要一个更好的电容器
我们将把它放在附近的LSC中
有了那个
我们现在可以开始制作一个
使用一个戴森球的电量、在16步、45秒内完成制作的EoH
再使用3个戴森球的电量
我们可以快速制作其他部分
然而，在做完这些东西之前
我们得解决一些事情
制作的最后一步应该很耗时
但其他步骤需要大量材料
主要问题是我们的电路生产
材料造成了堵塞
导致子网的储存量成了问题
因此是时候扩大电路厂的规模了
那是电路厂的第一层
我们慢慢地建好工厂每一层
由于新发现的工具，这总体上很容易
有了这些新电路
我们很快完成第一个EoH的制作
这是又一个有特殊要求的多方块
首先是需要改变游戏UI大小
来完整地看到它的用途
它每完成一次运行
我们将获得大量资源
但我们关心的是
浓缩的原始恒星等离子体混合物
和白矮星物质
然而
配方耗时实在太高了
总需求输入比我们每tick能输入的都多
所以我们可能会在最初的几次迭代中研究一些超频
为了帮助我们在这方面进行一些规划
任务书里这个电子表格可帮上大忙了
剩下要做的就是为鸿蒙之眼输入液体
这需要一些时间
一旦原材料足够
便可以将其开机
然而
看起来它不会产生任何东西
那是因为我们给它灌了太多的液体
这个奇特公式的意思是
如果你输入超过需求5%的液体，就不会有产物
所以要输入精确的数目
我们将使用涉及ae2和合成卡的复杂系统
慢慢给机器充电后
我们设法让它以完整的输出运行
还有一个不到一小时就能完成的配方
超频消耗了我们几天积累的能量
不管怎样
那台机器仍处于原始状态
我们想至少升级到完美
如果我们想制造熔融宇宙素
一种用于任何UXV部件的材料
然而
获得完美的鸿蒙之眼需要黑矮星物质
需要在先进及更高等级的配方中获得
想得到它们
我们缺少白矮星物质和无尽
DTPF已经足够多了
所以我们应该寻找更好的方法
例如用跨纬度对齐矩阵升级一台DTPF
那东西会让我们的无尽的生产速度提高20倍
白矮星物质已经成为一个主要问题
我们的产量已经太低了
我们的发电量甚至跟不上这么少的产量的消耗
为了更好地理解现状
我们可以回到电子表格
看看在不同超频下发电量和目标进度是怎么变化的
像这样得到第4级鸿蒙之眼是不行的
增加产量有很多方法
一个有趣的是升级时间膨胀场发生器
从而变成原本时间的1/4
但是增加20%的配方失败机会
问题是这些将花费白矮星物质
但是是以更合理的数目
那还需要一些时间
我们可以用来进一步升级电力生产
我们有那么多时间可以支配
我们建造了100多个戴森球
足以在三小时内充满一个终极电池
一旦我们收集到足够的白矮星物质
我们可以把时间膨胀场发生器升级到第三级
产量是第一级的3倍
并将我们的产量提高到1 mb/t
我们可以把剩下的部分用在第二台EoH上
为了避免再造一个复杂的液体输入系统
我们已经把复杂的部分拆出来
改成可以多台机器共用的形式
不管怎样，就像说的那样
我们现在生产白矮星物质的速度快了4倍
但要在合理的时间内到达第四级还是不够的
黑矮星物质需要T4才能生产
但只需要1/5的材料消耗我们就可以进入T3
在当前设置下
这没什么大不了的
它将允许使用t3维度
这还不会产生黑矮星物质
但会产生大量的白矮星物质
允许更快的进入T4
所以在我们花几个小时等待缺少材料的同时
我们可以去我们创造的袖珍宇宙中旅行
在那里我们可以欣赏星星的创造和毁灭
从中提取矮星物质
在探索了多个微型宇宙之后
我们收集了足够的材料
增加时空压缩场发生器的等级
这意味着我们现在可以容纳T3维度
从而产生4倍的白矮星物质
现在问题又变成装配线了
我们没有充分利用它们的潜力
我们有一些通用的
并没有用上它们的并行特性
以及其他需要手动为配方设置过滤的装配线
然而
我们刚刚注意到一个可以帮助我们解决所有问题的功能
并制作完美的装配线设置
一种允许同时在多条装配线上进行多配方并行制作的设置
想解释它是如何工作的不适合放在这个视频
但你可以在这里欣赏它有多好
这只是众多进行耗时配方制作的装配线中的一条
我们会想要更多的
但是在制作的时候
我们已经完成了T4鸿蒙
这将使我们可获得黑矮星物质
但目前的设置
产量太低了
所以我们做了更多的鸿蒙之眼
为其他升级储备大量白矮星物质
完美级的鸿蒙需要相当多的黑矮星物质
所以让我们看看如何得到它
到目前为止
那需要大约100个小时
并且是耗电的
我们可以通过制造更多戴森球来解决电量问题
我们可以制造更多T4鸿蒙来加快这个过程
但是我们可能不得不降低超频设置
最好的选择可能是一步一步来
就是先做T5鸿蒙
这将允许更快到达T6
到那时
我们注意到成功率越来越低
我们可以牺牲一些产量来增加成功率
一旦我们到达T6
我们就可以生产T7了
但是我们可能会想先做更多T6
并降低超频
当然还有
大规模生产那样的机器
开始对我们的实验性装配线给予过多负担
所以我们不得不添加更多
并将其无线链接
有了这个
我们现在有一群眼睛
最终产生了一些宇宙素
要使用它
我们先把它凝固成锭
然后将其压成块
用那些
我们现在可以制造宇宙素纳米蜂群
它有很多用途
但主要的是
磁流体约束恒星物质
这是用于UXV和MAX所有零部件的
但仍有一些材料我们无法获得
第一个是永恒
要获得它
我们从获得一些时间碎片开始
然后我们加入一份宇宙素纳米蜂群
获得时间协调催化剂
这将使我们产生永恒
但它会利用一些永恒奇点
我们能用永恒轻松生产它
但对于第一次循环
我们必须选择更昂贵的方式
而且
要从循环配方中获得更多的永恒
我们可以加入一些镄和钕等离子体
下一级的另一个主要成分是磁物质
这些东西是在太阳聚变异化器中产生的
然而
做这件事并不像看起来那么容易
首先
我们必须解锁神锻的最后一次升级
这需要大量的引力子碎片
这意味着必须更多地使用神锻来完成里程碑
一个简单的想法是处理更多的东西
出于各种原因，我们无法一步生产大量材料
我们将任务拆分到多个CPU
事实证明
制作2^29个钢锭只需1t
我们重复这个过程很多次
去获得新碎片
然而，这些并没有让我们走得太远
所以我们回退一些不需要的升级
然后再升级一次之后
这也消耗完了我们所有的真·终极电池
我们又一次用完了碎片
幸运地
有一个奇怪的循环配方
可以让我们轻松烧制溢出int32数量的东西
然而
我们现在达到了转换里程碑的最大值
并且需要做其他事情
比如加热一些氮气
把它加热成等离子会消耗很多能量
从而帮助我们达到下一个充电里程碑
有了那个
就剩下最后一次升级了
主要问题是我们需要极其多的电池
目前
我们唯一缺少的就是重拉多X
让我们梳理一下目前的事
制作这些电池需要套娃
意味着情况会呈指数级恶化
幸运地
我们解锁了制造电池的更好方法
这大大降低了成本
然而
仍然消耗了等量的超能硅岩制作部件
因为我们的产能不够
我们一直在用重拉多X生产它
我们可以增加产量
但有更好的方法来解决这个问题
我们可以跳过更多东西
通过使用一些新获得的材料
但这需要相当多的宇宙素
所以我们最好多长点心眼
或者不止一个
让我们更具体一点
要在一天之内拿到1000万宇宙素
我们需要100个满配EoH
所以目前
我们最好想个更好的办法制造超能硅岩
增加矿产才是正道
但我们还有别的办法
通过在QFT中加入一些催化剂
我们可以增加产量
并将更多的输出集中在我们关心的东西
这是我们制作电池唯一缺少的材料
然后我们花了些时间挂机
解锁下一个催化剂里程碑
这样我们就有足够的碎片来完成路径
这将使我们能够处理磁物质
然而生产这种材料并不容易
并非往机器里随便扔东西一样简单
在解锁太阳聚变异化器的磁物质模式后
我们必须完成它的小游戏
一开机
这台机器会给我们一小堆昂贵的材料
然后是一些时空相关的液滴
想得到磁物质
我们必须将两种流体数量的差值乘144
将小撮粉转化为对应数量的等离子体
所以我们很快就想出了一种快速获取所需等离子的方法
并把它输入给异化器
还有它给我们的另外两种液体
有了这个
我们终于得到了第一个磁物质
现在的问题是找到一种自动化该过程的方法
也许
这实际上就像向一台新机器随意扔东西一样简单
我们要做的就是确保
它总是有14种不同的等离子体可供使用
我们可以把另外两种液体循环回去
因为这个装置不需要做任何数学运算
现在我们有了磁物质
我们终于可以制作UXV部件了
我不得不说
这是一个非常复杂的马达
因为它不仅在一些绕组中包含湿件主机
它的轴承球内还包含UXV级电路
不管怎样
在快速研究UXV能源仓后
我们升级了电动聚爆压缩机
这将使我们能够解锁所有的配方
比如减半制造蓝框岩浆时宇宙素消耗
为了进一步减少材料的使用
我们想要一条新的UXV部件装配线
但我们很快就意识到
我们的宇宙素产量相当低
,所以我们开始制作第一个满配EoH
都是由鸿蒙部件制成的
它现在无比强大
可以包含整个太阳系
它不仅会释放出游戏中存在的大量原材料
它也会生产比它消耗更多的能量
要以合适的速度加载它
我们现在可以使用巨型输入仓
但那东西仍然只能产生1.6L/s的宇宙素
要获得一条UXV部件装配线
我们需要2700万升
不需要太多就能明白我们无处可去
即使是堆更多这机器
所以我们要找到比顶配更好的方法
我们想出了一个非常有趣的解决方案
星阵
将其放入鸿蒙之眼后将允许并行
但它有一些缺点
我们首先注意到的是
电力输出为负
这样工作会消耗原始恒星等离子体混合物
那些材料也将入不敷出
那主要是成功率低造成的
但我们可以降级一次扩张场发生器
回到正产率
现在只需要搞明白
我们需要多少星阵才能获得足够多的宇宙素
以及如何补充耗电
不管怎样
因为我们的旧设备生产不了足够的材料
我们把它拆掉以便回收利用
来制作我们第一个星阵
那个东西
加上一个几乎满配的鸿蒙之眼
已经比我们旧顶配鸿蒙强五倍了
但这还不够
因此，我们开始大规模生产星阵
有了这个
我们现在正以指数增加宇宙素产量
至少在电池耗尽之前是的
但我们设法及时完成了UXV部件装配线
和以往一样
这台机器将使用更少的材料来生产各个组件
这次我们甚至跳过了材料的压缩
但我们还是要插入部分电路
不管怎样
既然我们已经完成了UXV的所有工作
并解锁整合包里的所有东西
我们只剩下最后一个挑战了
但我想这是我们下一集该做的
今天的教训是
永远把最酷的东西藏起来
这样最后一集就更精彩了
拜拜
（这里升了两级时间膨胀场，所以时间是(1/2)^2=1/4，成功率减少9.25*2=18.5%）
（之后用EoH指代鸿蒙之眼）
（俗称蓝框岩浆）
（keep eye on sth：留意某物
这里双关，eye直接指EoH）